High availability, also called HA design is critical and modern systems.
高可用性 也称为 HA 设计 是关键的现代系统
HA systems has standby component's ready in
HA 系统具有备用组件已就绪
waiting to takeover supporting your application at a moments notice.
在时刻注意支持您的应用程序
The standby systems have up to the second copies of your data.
备用系统具有数据的第二个副本
Today's platforms are expected to be highly available.
今天的平台预计将会高度可用
Building for fail over must be considered at
必须考虑构建故障转移
every level of a system and must be part of the initial plan.
系统的每个级别 并且必须是初始计划的一部分
Allowing for any individual component to fail and
允许任何单个组件失败 并且
having a standby system able to take over is no small task.
拥有一个能够接管的备用系统是没有小任务的
But HA design allows for platform systems to
但是 HA 设计允许平台系统
remain available regardless of any given server failing.
无论任何给定服务器发生故障 都将保持可用
Customers rely on software as a service systems.
客户依赖软件作为服务系统
Thus HA design is table stakes,
因此 房委会的设计是有表利害关系的
not only critical infrastructure applications are highly available these days.
这几天不仅是关键的基础设施应用
Netflix, for example, has highly redundant geographically distributed platform.
例如  Netflix 具有高度冗余的地理分布平台
In this course, you'll look and going beyond handling individual component failures,
在此过程中 您将查看并超越处理个别组件故障
and how you can handle entire data center outrages
以及如何处理整个数据中心的事件